non-profit. We're focused on close-of-a-gap on care costs and coverage for hardworking Americans.
How do you make money? We get paid based on the savings we generate for colleagues.
Cool. Yep. The insurance for the health insurance industry is the most broken model in America.
That's by writing better benefits to the companies that are employing set people.
So I sell the super. Yeah, we sell them businesses. Our focus is 50 plus to the
account. So adders.com, right? We're above that size, right? Yeah. So how many close do you sell a month
off of for four partners? Honestly, our close-of-a-gap is only about 10%. Oh, no, absolutely.
How many absolute accounts do you post? Probably about one account per month.
She's up. So you pitch me. Bring help your trap to retain talent and increase probability.
And I can typically tell them just based on like, if you tell them coming employees you guys have
at acquisition level, what do you pay in? Well, yeah, but it's just a hundred. Just round it.
So I can tell you right off the bat, I'm going to say you're about 200,000. But that sounds like
scam. Truthfully, that sounds like a scam. Like how the hell am I going to save you $200,000,
which most people just like me, they run away. Can I give you a different angle for the pitch?
Please? Like, hey, we'll save you 15% on whatever your number is in the briefing. We can do that
is because we are an unprofit. So we take the profit that most businesses like here's the
industry average profit margin for business in my space is 20%. We take that 20% and make it zero.
And that's your own goes to you. That's our business works. That's me. Mays pops up.
I very like that. So I'm losing 10%. Yeah.
It's like with the offer you have your sales process sucks. And so like, I just say like that,
that would be my first area of focus because you could probably get a triple in the business of
there. So doing nothing else.